We'll be right back.
So Big Bro Frankie sacrificed himself to save you guys and now he's...
Yeah, that's right.
He was trying to rescue Robin and help us escape with her.
We need to hurry or we won't make it in time.
Look, the lights are the Nightless Island.
It's Eni's lobby.
Really?
I can't believe we made it.
All right!
Now we can rescue Bro.
Nightless Island?
Yeah.
The sun never stops shining there, so it's nightless.
They sometimes call the Judicial Island a daytime island too.
Is that so?
We found him!
The Giant Yogurt!
Gravity!
Luffy!
Safety!
Hey!
Sorgie!
Who the heck is that?
It's gonna be totally fine, okay?
It's Strawhead!
Yes!
Looks like we caught up with him, no problem.
Well, now that we've found the others,
it's time for our date with the world government.
Hell yeah, it is!
Okay, this is it! Now approaching Enny's lobby!
All hands, get ready for a showdown!
At last, after five long years,
the time has finally come for all eight members of CP9 to be reunited.
This should be a time of celebration.
But instead, I'll ask...
What's the meaning of this?!
Your orders were to assassinate the leaders of the revolution.
But according to this article, not only did you kill those three,
but twenty others as well!
What happened?!
If you have an excuse, I'd like to hear it!
Yo-yo-y!
My most sincere apologies and pardons, Chief.
Everything is entirely, unreservedly, completely my fault.
Stop that, Kumadori!
A real man doesn't bow his head to anybody.
I'll explain everything that happened to the Chief,
so shut up and get a hold of yourself.
Yo-yo-y! I can't apologize enough.
And so, if need be, I'll shoulder the blame by taking my own life!
Don't be so melodramatic!
Yo-yo-y!
It happened like this, Chief.
We followed the plan to the letter.
We infiltrated their forces and were all ready for the assassination.
But somehow, the enemy managed to find out about our plans!
Probably cause I was talking about them all over town, cha-ba-ba!
You again?!
What's wrong with you?!
And what's the point of having a zipper on your mouth if you don't even use the damn thing?!
This little butter mouth problem of yours has got to stop!
Understand?!
We're secret agents!
We've got secrets to keep!
I want to do it on purpose, cha-ba-ba!
Why don't you top about me?!
You can't do anything about it now, cha-ba-ba!
There's no need to blame, fukuro!
I don't need a cha-ba-ba!
I take full responsibility!
Second rule!
Iron body!
I can't even die right!
Oh, just get it over with, you bastard!
You've been doing everyone a favor!
That accidentally we talked about it, cha-ba-ba!
Shut up!
Enough, I understand.
Hot, hot, hot!
I spilled my coffee again, damn it!
Oh, by the way, I heard Nero didn't work out.
Whatever.
The game could snipe around and far away.
In my game, it's straight at home.
Ooh-loo-la-la-doo!
Whether you're a man or a mouse,
Lock on!
I will put your heart in my sights!
No one knows what secrets
Knows what secrets hide behind this glass and blind game.
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, la, la, there is no escape.
Sniper, Sniper, Sniper, Sniper.
Sniper keeps true.
Sniper King from Sniper Island? For real?
That's right. I'm a close friend of Usopp's.
I'm here because he asked me to aid you on this perilous journey.
He's a superhero.
I knew it. I could totally tell because of the mask and cape.
Amazing. I've never seen one before.
So wearing a mask and cape means he has superpowers?
Of course. Everybody in a mask and cape is a superhero.
Really?
Isn't that Usopp?
I'm glad you're safe, Usopp.
That's the long-nosed guy that busted into the freaky house.
That's the guy that got taken away with Bro.
Yeah.
Totally. No question.
It's nice to meet you.
Likewise.
That's one of the guys we met at the shift station.
Yeah.
Can I have your autograph?
Sure.
That makes me wonder, where did Usopp go?
He's safe. There's no need to worry about him.
Anyway, he told me the most important thing right now is saving your friend Robin.
Then he left.
Yep.
He's absolutely right.
So, uh, so where exactly is this Sniper Island?
Hm? I'll tell you.
Oh, the ring carries my name.
It's inside of your heart.
From Sniper Island far away.
Sing it!
Hey, Nami.
Huh?
Yeah?
What is it?
When I take aim.
Huh?
What is it?
When I take aim.
Just a second.
Oh, the wind carries my name
From Sniper Island far away
Sing it!
Hey, Nami.
Huh?
Yeah?
What is it?
Just a second.
The rest of you idiots should hear this too.
Before we go to rescue Robin, there's something you need to know.
If there's a buster call, you'll be obliterated.
Long ago, an island was erased.
Five vice admirals and ten battleships are a terrifying force for anyone to behold.
But for a child to see them destroy her home, well, it's nothing short of a nightmare.
Those thoughts have haunted her for years.
And now that her old nightmare bears its fangs at her companions, she no longer has the will to resist us.
You bastards.
You knew and you used that.
Of course we did.
Those CP9 guys are controlling Robin by using her childhood fears against her.
I'm not making excuses for not being able to save her.
I just wanted to make it clear that even if we march in to get her back, it doesn't necessarily mean that she'll be willing to return with us.
No, it's over.
This is the last time you'll see me.
None of that matters!
I won't stand for this!
Damn Robin!
It's not her fault!
Of course it is, Nami!
Why doesn't she want us to rescue her?
It doesn't make sense!
Because she doesn't want to feel responsible for all the awful things that'll happen to our crew once we do.
I don't care about all that!
If we don't rescue her, she's gonna be killed, isn't she?
There's no way she wants to die, so we're gonna save her!
Well, of course she doesn't want to die, but still...
Let it go.
This doesn't change what we have to do.
We'll save her either way.
I'm gonna beat up every last one of them!
There's a new move I want to try!
Hey guys, take a look at this.
I came to this island once before to do some maintenance on the railway.
I drew this from what I could remember.
It's a rough sketch of the overall layout of Annie's lobby.
The Gates of Justice are located at the back of the island.
The only way to get to them is through the Tower of Law.
What's that big black thing?
It represents the waterfall.
Huh?
Yeah.
Once we're inside, you'll see.
If we don't rescue Frankie and Nico Robin before they pass through the main gate and into the Gates of Justice,
then that's it.
It's over.
And why's that?
It doesn't matter where they take her to, we'll just keep on fighting them until we get Robin back!
We explained this before we left Water 7, remember?
Once we pass that gate, the only two places we can go are Navy Headquarters or the Deep Sea Prison.
No matter what happens, we have to settle this before they reach those rear gates.
Yeah, pretty much.
On top of that, even if we all rush the island at the same time,
the only ones capable of going up against those CP9 guys are you, Straw Hats.
After seeing what you can do, I know how strong you are.
That's why I think you should stay behind once we get there.
Give us five minutes, then charge through to the main island in Rocketman.
The Frankie family and Gally Law will go in first and break open the main gate and the main island front gate so the train can pass through.
I'm sure we'll suffer a lot of casualties, but remember, once you're in, keep going no matter what.
Don't look back.
We've only got a little over 60 people.
The enemy forces probably have somewhere between 2,000 and 3,000.
Our best chance for victory is for you Straw Hats to concentrate on CP9 and leave the rest of the Marines to us.
Right. I got it.
Okay, folks, we're pulling up to the front of the island.
While we're here, take a look at the sky behind Innie's lobby.
Behold the Gates of Justice.
Whoa!
That's huge!
It's not a...
No one one
because you have to turn the light into your sleight.
We gaze on these deadlines.
All at the same time tale,
I'm afraid Straw Hat Luffy has entered the main island, sir.
What? Why the hell did you let him do that?
What's going on over there?
Get out of my way!
Any idiot should know what it means to attack any's lobby,
and if they don't, we'll have to teach them.
We're coming, Robin!
On the next One Piece, Luffy cuts through.
Big showdown on the Judicial Island.
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!